ILGWU Boston Joint Board Records 5780/055
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Company Files, 1947-2000
  - Styleader Fashions, Inc., 1954-1987 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Styleader Fashions, Inc., 1954-1987 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Styleader Fashions, Inc., 1954-1987 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Summit Sportswear, 1980-1987 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Stylerite, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Tick Tock Frocks, Inc., 1977 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Tileston Co., 1976-1987 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Time Fashions, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - T and N, Inc., 1970-1983 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Toggett Mfg. Co., 1976 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Warren Dress Co., 1970-1980 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Woonsocket Coat, Inc., 1978-1983 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Woonsocket Sportswear, 1973-1978 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Worcester Knitting, 1966-1999 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Worcester Knitting, 1966-1999 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Worcester Knitting, 1966-1999 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Benefits, 1988-1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Benefits, 1988-1995 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Boston City Counsel, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Contracts-Information, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Contracts-Settlements, 1976-1980 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Bert Cooper, Mfg., 1976-1980 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence-Abner Kravitz (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence-Ralph Roberts (Fall River), 1974-1979 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence-Members (Connecticut), 1984-1992 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Michael Dukakis (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - ESL (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Health and Safety Manual, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Industrial Development Working Group, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - International Locals, Joint Boards, and District Councils, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Labor History, 1987-1993 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Ceil Leshyk Investigation/Delores Medeiros, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Mass. Board of Conciliation and Arbitration, 1970-1980 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Registration of Contractors, 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Reports-Connecticut, 1974-1979 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Marie Tramontano, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - University of Connecticut Educational Seminar, 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Fashion Forward I, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Fashion Forward II, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Fashion Forward III, 1990-1992 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Fashion Forward IV, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - International Labor Movement, 1993-1996 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - International Labor/Garment Industry--Central America, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - International Labor/Garment Industry--Central America, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    Leslie Faye Central America
  - International Labor/Garment Industry--Europe General, 1989-1995 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - International Labor/Garment Industry--Europe, Italy, GFT, 1986-1994 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - International Labor/Garment Industry--Pakistan, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - International Labor Organization/ILO, 1993-1995 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Labor-Management Cooperation, 1987-1994 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Labor-Management Cooperation--UAW, 1986-1995 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Local/Regional Files; Local 155, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Long Island Apparel Labor-Management Committee Grant (Final Report), 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - New York State Legislature-Line Item, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Needle Trades Action Project (NTAP), 1985-1992 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    1 of 3
  - Needle Trades Action Project (NTAP), 1985-1992 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    2 of 3
  - Needle Trades Action Project (NTAP), 1985-1992 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    3 of 3
  - Apparel Industry Studies, 1988-1993 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Council for American Fashion, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Fashion Exports New Economic Policy and Marketing Group Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Fashion Exports New York, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Fashion Reports and Publications, 1990-1994 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    (includes Fashion Forward)
  - Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1987-1991 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1991-1994 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - GIDC News, 1992-1995 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Pennsylvania Industry/Government, 1989-1991 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Pennsylvania Garment Industry, 1990-1995 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - "Solidarity 85" Production, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 20)